http://www.kaman.com/privacy-policy

Women Advocating Leadership at Kaman
For the past 70 years Kaman has been recognized for technical breakthroughs and innovative solutions to critical aerospace challenges.
Company Facts
Aerospace Capabilities
Stay
Our Solutions
Our Solutions - Description - Corporate Menu Kaman is comprised of the following product groups: Aerosystems, Fuzing & Precision Products, Specialty Bearings & Engineered Products, and Seals, Springs, & Contacts. Together, these platforms allow us to provide quality service to customers across aerospace, defense, medical, and industrial sectors.
Solutions
Aerosystems
Fuzing & Precision Products
Specialty Bearings & Engineered Products
Seals, Springs, & Contacts
Stay
Investors
Investors
Investor & Stock Purchase Information
Convertible Notes and Warrants - Conversion Rate Adjustments
Sign Up to Receive Email Alerts
Since our founding, the company has grown both organically and through acquisitions to create a global Aerospace business.
Latest Investor Presentation
2019 Annual Report
Stock Quote
Stay
Careers
Careers
Current Job Listings
See Yourself at Kaman
Working at Kaman
Contact
At Kaman, we are always looking for a better way. Whether we are helping keep our troops safe or pioneering safer ways to fly the globe, we approach every challenge with an innovation mindset.
Current Job Listings
Corporate Responsibility
Stay
Contact
Home
Our Company Our Company
Leadership Team
History of Innovation
Careers Careers
Where Do I Fit?
Working at Kaman
Contact
EEO-1 Voluntary Self Identification Form
News
Events
Media
Governance
Contact
You are hereHome » Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Kaman Corporation's policy is to protect personally identifiable information provided to us at the Kaman Site from unauthorized access. Personally identifiable information means data that can identify you, including your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address.
Information Collected
You can visit the Kaman Site without providing any personally identifiable information. However, we may need to collect such data from you for a specific purpose, such as when you request information or to monitor user traffic on the site or for other purposes. There are also portions of the websites of certain Kaman subsidiaries that permit you to register for the purpose of purchasing products or services and personally identifiable information will be collected for that purpose. The Kaman Site is not intended for use by persons under the age of 13. Kaman does not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from or about children or markets its products and services to children.
Kaman subsidiary websites or other listed sites may have their own privacy policy statement, in which case any additional terms in such policy will apply to your accessing of the subsidiary website.
Cookies
Kaman may use cookies on this site. Cookies are small text files sent to and stored on users’ computers that allow Websites, such as Kaman.com, to recognize repeat users, facilitate users’ access to sites, and allow sites to compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements. Cookies do not damage users’ computers or files. If users do not want cookies to be accessible by Kaman, most browser programs allow users to deny or disable the use of cookies.
Use of Collected Information
Kaman uses the personally identifiable information that you provide only to respond to your inquiry or process your request. Kaman may need to share this information with companies that have been hired to perform services, however, those service providers are required to use the information only for the service they have been hired to provide (e.g., when you pay for a purchase with a credit card). Kaman does not share personally identifiable information with any third parties for marketing use. Kaman will release such information if you direct us to, if we are required by law to do so, or under other limited circumstances as permitted by law.
Security
The Kaman Site uses various systemic and administrative means to protect personally identifiable information from unauthorized or improper access. Within Kaman, access to such information is limited to those having a need to know in order to process your inquiry.
Contacting Kaman
If you have any questions about this policy, please contact us.
If you are an EU employee or customer and would like to request your information, please do so through our Data Subject Request Portal.
